http://www.realcold.co.nz/legal/privacy-policy.aspx

Realcold – People Product Partnerships
Go to New Zealand site
HomeProducts
ProductsCatalogueProduct BrandsGree WarrantyResources
ResourcesCase studiesBrochuresMaterial safety data sheetsPressure temperature chart News
NewsLatest news updatesEventsPromotionsIndustry LinksAbout Us
About UsRealcold's promise & valuesHistoryCommercial air-conditioningDomestic air-conditioningIndustrial refrigerationCommercial refrigerationContact Us
You are here / Home
/ Privacy Policy
View our latest catalogue
Privacy Policy
At Realcold we're totally committed to protecting your personal
information and will look after the information you entrust to us
and keep it safely and securely.
Your Information
We're always aiming to improve what we do and the more we know
about you, the better we can serve you. The personal information
that you supply to us through www.realcold.com.au enables us to
personalise and improve your experience and relationship with us.
It gives us a greater understanding of you, so that we can provide
you details of services and promotions that we feel would be of
interest to you. Your personal information is collected in a
variety of ways such as filling out our contact form.
Disclosing Information
Realcold may share information about visitors in aggregate with
third parties including advertisers, business partners and
sponsors, to understand visitor trends and patterns, and to manage
and improve our service. Such information will be anonymous so that
visitor's privacy is protected.
Realcold may disclose your information in response to a threat
of legal proceedings as for example in response to a Court Order or
a subpoena. Further, if Realcold is requested by the police or any
regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal
activities to provide your personal information or other data
collected about you and/or information concerning your activities
whilst using the website at www.realcold.com.au we shall do so. We
also reserve the right to disclose individually identifiable
information to third parties where a complaint arises concerning
your use of the above website, and that use is deemed by us to be
inconsistent with the terms and conditions.
www.realcold.com.au may contain links to other sites where
information practices may be different. For example, if you "click"
on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off this site.
This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners that
may use our logo as part of a co-branding agreement. You should
consult the other site's privacy notices as Realcold is not
responsible and has no control over information that is submitted
to or collected by such third parties.
Realcold may also use available technology to determine which
areas of www.realcold.com.au you visit and the activities which you
participate in. This information will be used for the purposes of
managing your account, business development, trend analysis and
marketing. If Realcold should decide to change its privacy policy,
those changes will be published on this page so that you are always
aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what
circumstances we disclose it.
It is possible that Realcold could merge with or be acquired by
another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you
should expect that Realcold would share some or all of your
information in order to continue to provide the service. You will
receive notice of such event (to the extent it occurs) and we will
require that the new combined entity follow the privacy practices
which you have agreed to on registration with us.
Keep reading
Realcold
© 2020 Realcold is a BEIJER REF company.
